Finding Aid for the Lady Agnes Anne Adams Papers LSC.1361
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Correspondence (Box 4)
  - Fortnightly Review, London. Letter to Lady Adams, 1930.; 1 item. Signed H.H.L. Dickson. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Farrand, Beatrix. Letters to Mrs. Spencer Thorpe. (Box 4, Folder 11-24)
    - 1940-1941., 8 items. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 1942-1943., 8 items. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - 1944., 14 items. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - 1945., 8 items. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - 1946., 11 items. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - 1947., 13 items. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - 1948., 19 items. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - 1949., 12 items. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - 1950., 9 items. (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - 1951-1952., 9 items. (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - 1953-1954., 11 items. (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - 1955-1956., 9 items. (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - 1957., 6 items. (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Letters and cards, undated; 11 items. (Box 4, Folder 24)
      Includes 3 envelopes.
  - Ephemera regarding Beatrix Farrand., 4 items. (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Contents: 3 postcards of Reef Point, Beatrix Farrand's home in Bar Harbor, Maine, and a note regarding Beatrix Farrand's training in landscape design.
  - Freeman, Allen and Katherine. Letter to Dr. and Mrs. [John] Adams., undated; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Grand Central Terminal, New York. Letter to Mrs. Spencer Thorpe, 1954.; 1 item. Signed E.G. Fischer. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Howells, Mildred. Letter to Lady Adams, 1934.; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Knopf (Alfred A.) Incorporated, New York. Letter to Lady Adams, 1940.; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Moore, Ernest Carroll and Dorothea., 1936, 1942, undated; 4 items. (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Osgood, Charles G. Letter to Lady Adams, 1935.; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Rackham, Edyth. Letter to Lady Adams, undated; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Scott, Jessie. Letter to Lady Adams, 1939.; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Stone, William Standish. Letter to Lady Adams, 1940.; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 34)
    With prospectus for Teri Taro From Bora Bora by William Standish Stone enclosed.
  - Stover, Isabelle. Letter to Mrs. Spencer Thorpe, 1952, 1957.; 3 items. (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Unidentified., 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Valley Club of Montecito, Santa Barbara. Letters to Mrs. Spencer Thorpe, 1945, 1951.; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Posters (Box 5)
  - Announcements for the John Adams Lecture, UCLA, for the years, 1938-1939, 1940-1941.; 2 items. (Box 5)
  - Whakarewarewa [?], New Zealand., 1899.; 1 item. 29 × 22.5 cm. Watercolor. Signed ASB. (Box 5)